Guide to the Vassar College Student Materials Collection, 1859-2025 (bulk 1867-1950)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES V. LETTERS, 1859 - circa 1960
  - VC 1879 — Jackson, Helen (Basfield) — to Ann Scholfield, 1875, 1877; (2 letters) (Box 70)
  - VC Ex 1879 — Kiliani, Lillian (Taylor) — to Grandmother "my dear Mithery", 1873, 1877; (5 letters) (Box 70)
  - VC 1880 — Noyes, Emma (Hartman) — to H. Rachel Swan (VC 1880), undated; (1 letter) (Box 71)
  - VC 1880 — Pratt, Mary (Morris) — to mother, 1874, 1877-1880; (8 letters) (Box 72)
  - VC Ex 1880 — Skinner, Laura A. — to and from Frances May Bromby (VC 1879) and Agnes L. Bromby, 1876 December - 1881 December (Box 17)
  - VC Ex 1880 — Skinner, Laura A. — to and from Frances May Bromby (VC 1879) and Agnes L. Bromby, 1877 February - 1882 December (Box 18)
  - VC Ex 1880 — Skinner, Laura A. — to and from Frances May Bromby (VC 1879) and Agnes L. Bromby, 1881 January - November (Box 19)
  - VC Ex 1881 — Gay, Mary W. — to Belle [probably Frances (Bronson) Jones], 1883 September - November (Box 185)
  - VC 1881-1882 [Preparatory] — Vincent, Anna (Mabbett) — to Aunt Anne, 1881 September 25; (1 letter) (Box 74)
  - VC 1882 — Wyman, Anne (Southworth) — from family, (15 letters) (Box 75)
  - VC 1883 — Johnson, Caroline (Curtiss) — from father, 1878 October 16; (1 letter) (Box 70)
  - VC 1883 — Jones, Martha (Boyd) — to mother, 1882; (1 letter) (Box 70)
  - VC 1884 — Griffith, Caroline — from L. Blanche, W.L. Dean, Flora Easton, Mary L. Hutchins, and Helen Ramlow, 1878-1885; (19 letters) (Box 69)
  - VC Ex 1885 — Hagerman, Mary [Ella] (Comstock) — to brother, 1881-1882; (4 letters) (Box 69)
  - VC 1886-1888 [Special] — Eaton, Julia (Hammer) — to Emma Hoadley Tenney, 1888 February 26; (2 letters) (Box 67)
  - VC 1888 — Faust, Frances (Patterson) — to George M. Patterson, 1888 April 8; (1 letter) (Box 68)
  - VC 1888 — Hatcher, Orie Latham — to Mr. Pace, 1887 November 13, 22; (2 letters) (Box 69)
  - VC 1888 — Stephenson, Mary (Sheldon) — to Sate, 1884; (3 letters) (Box 73)
  - VC 1888 — Strong, Eliza (McCreery) — to family, (1 letter) (Box 73)
  - VC 1889 — Finley, Charlotte (Deming) — to Cousin, 1886 November 25; (1 letter) (Box 68)
  - VC 1891 — Copeland, May I. — to mother (bound transcripts with some photographs and original letters), 1887-1890 (Box 67)
  - VC 1892 — Banfield, Edith C. — to family, 1888 Fall; (3 letters) (Box 64)
  - VC 1893 — Wood, Harriet A. — to Nettie (Brand) DeWitt (VC Ex 1896), 1892 April 17; (1 letter) (Box 75)
  - VC 1894 — Vanderburgh, Caroline — to family, 1890 September 21 - October 19 (Box 209)
  - VC 1896 — Hollingworth, Ruth (Mann) — to Alice M. Howland (VC 1896), 1895 June 6; (1 letter) (Box 70)
  - VC 1896 — Johnson, Mignonette Bird — to family, 1892 December - 1895 May; (5 folders, 82 letters) (Box 212)
  - VC Ex 1896 — DeWitt, Nettie (Brand) — to family, 1892-1894; (22 letters) (Box 66)
  - VC 1897 — Kirkland, Winifred — to Jennie S. Liebman, 1893, 1895; (3 letters) (Box 70)
  - VC 1897 — Mansfield, Adelaide (Claflin) — to family, 1893 October - 1895 March (Box 20)
  - VC 1897 — Mansfield, Adelaide (Claflin) — to family, 1895 April - 1897 (Box 21)
  - VC 1897 — McGill, Beatrice (Shaw) — to family, 1887-1888 (Box 186)
  - VC 1897 — Stockton, Madeleine (Traver) — to unknown, undated; (1 letter) (Box 73)
  - VC 1899 — Greer, Florence — Mary A. Mineah (VC 1870), 1895 November; (1 letter) (Box 69)
  - VC 1900 — Merrill, Isabel (Trowbridge) — to family, 1896 August - 1898 May (Box 139)
  - VC 1900 — Merrill, Isabel (Trowbridge) — to family, 1898 May - 1900 May (Box 140)
  - VC 1902 — Townsend, Fanny (Simpson) — to family, 1898 May - 1900 (Box 24)
  - VC 1902 — Townsend, Fanny (Simpson) — to family, 1899 September - 1900 June (Box 25)
  - VC 1902 — Townsend, Fanny (Simpson) — to family, 1900 September - 1901 June (Box 26)
  - VC 1902 — Townsend, Fanny (Simpson) — to family and from Cousin Patrick, 1901 September - 1903 June (Box 27)
  - VC 1903 — Morgan, Katharine — to mother as well as letters from friends from Kansas City, the VC Class of 1903, and elsewhere, 1870, 1901-1915 (Box 200)
  - VC 1904 — Adams, Ruth — to parents, 1900 September - 1902 April (Box 1)
  - VC 1904 — Adams, Ruth — to family, 1900 September - 1901 June (Box 2)
  - VC 1904 — Adams, Ruth — to family, 1902 April - November (Box 3)
  - VC 1904 — Adams, Ruth — to and from family, Eloise Ellery, Edith K. Hawes, Florence Pelton, and Elizabeth Thelburg, 1903 January - December (Box 4)
  - VC 1904 — Adams, Ruth — to family and from Flora A. Clarke (aunt), 1904 January - June (Box 5)
  - VC 1904 — Crippen, Ruth H. — to family, 1900-1904; (5 letters) (Box 65)
  - VC 1904 — Hawes, Edith K. — to Ruth Adams, undated; (1 letter) (Box 69)
  - VC 1904 — Taylor, Lea D. — to family, 1900 Fall; (8 letters) (Box 73)
  - VC 1904 — Van Deusen, Marjorie H. — to family and from Caroline, 1900 October - 1902 (Box 33)
  - VC 1905 — Eaton, Esther — to Miss Shipp, undated; (1 letter) (Box 67)
  - VC 1905 — Johns, Roberta T. — to and from family, 1901 September - 1902 June (Box 38)
  - VC 1905 — Johns, Roberta T. — to family, 1902 September - 1903 May (Box 39)
  - VC 1905 — Ross, Caroline (Barnes) — to mother and unknown recipients, 1902-1903; (10 letters) (Box 72)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family, 1901 September - 1911 May (Box 12)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family, 1902 April - December (Box 13)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family, 1903 (Box 14)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family, 1904 (Box 15)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family, 1905 January - June (Box 16)
  - VC 1905 — Shipp, Margaret M. — to family [transcripts], 1901-1905 (Box 212)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston — to family and Jean McGirr, 1902 September - 1903 March (Box 28)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston — to family, 1903 April - December (Box 29)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston — to family and Jean McGirr, 1904 (Box 30)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston — to family and Jean McGirr, 1905 January - October (Box 31)
  - VC 1906 — McGirr, Alice Thurston — to family and Jean McGirr, 1905 November - 1906 June (Box 32)
  - VC 1906 — Smith, Sidney (Lewis) — to family, 1902 September - 1904 December (Box 34)
  - VC 1906 — Smith, Sidney (Lewis) — to family, 1905 January - 1906 June (Box 35)
  - VC 1906 — Van der Veer, Elizabeth K. — to mother, 1906 June 21 (Box 74)
  - VC 1906-1907 — Elwell, Marion F. — to family, 1904 March 4; (1 letter) (Box 67)
  - VC 1906-1907 — Elwell, Marion F. — from family, 1905 April - May (Box 67)
  - VC 1909 — Angell, Pauline K. — to family, 1906-1909 (Box 200)
  - VC 1909 — Ryerson, Margery A. — to family, 1905-1908; (4 letters) (Box 72)
  - VC 1910 — Marshall, Katherine (Manson) — to Emma Stewart, undated; (1 letter) (Box 75)
  - VC Ex 1910 — Worthing, Margaret (Fletcher) — to family, 1907-1911; (30 letters) (Box 75)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — to and from family, "Allan," Jenny Ware, and "Jessie E.", [1907?] September - 1908 December (Box 6)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — to and from family, "Ella" and "Genevieve", 1909 January - June (Box 7)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — to and from family, "William," "Nelson," and Alice Frost, 1909 September - 1910 February (Box 8)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher)— to and from family, "William," and Edith (Wyman) Wilson (VC Ex 1910), 1910 March - November (Box 9)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — to family and from Esther, 1911-1916 (Box 10)
  - VC 1911 — MacCoy, Marjorie Newell — to family, 1907 October - 1909 March (Box 40)
  - VC 1911 — MacCoy, Marjorie Newell — to family and Harriet Jean, 1909 March - 1910 May (Box 41)
  - VC 1911 — MacCoy, Marjorie Newell — to family and Harriet Jean [transcripts], 1907 October - 1910 (Box 41)
  - VC 1912 — Stimson, Dorothy — to family, 1909 January - 1910 December (Box 142)
  - VC 1912 — Stimson, Dorothy — to parents, 1911 January - December (Box 143)
  - VC 1912 — Stimson, Dorothy — to parents, 1912 January - December (Box 144)
  - VC 1912 — Valentine, Gertrude C. — to family, 1908 September - December (Box 44)
  - VC 1912 — Valentine, Gertrude C. — to family, 1909 January - May (Box 45)
  - VC 1912 — Valentine, Gertrude C. — to family, 1909 September - 1910 February (Box 46)
  - VC 1912 — Valentine, Gertrude C. — to family, 1910 March - November (Box 47)
  - VC 1912 — Valentine, Gertrude C. — to family, 1911 January - June (Box 48)
  - VC 1912 — White, Katherine M. (Brown) — to family, 1908 September -1909 December (Box 42)
  - VC 1912 — White, Katherine M. (Brown) — to family, 1910 January - 1912 March (Box 43)
  - VC 1913 — Fitt, Harriet (Bradley) — to family, 1910 January - April; (31 letters) (Box 68)
  - VC Ex 1913 — Daniell, Margaret — to family, 1909 Fall (Box 66)
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French) — to family, 1910 September - 1911 May (Box 11)
  - VC 1914 — Eldridge, Muriel (Tilden) — to family, 1911 January - 1913 June; (69 letters) (Box 49)
  - VC 1914 — Eldridge, Muriel (Tilden) — to family, 1913 September - 1914 June; (24 letters) (Box 50)
  - VC 1914 — Eldridge, Muriel (Tilden) — to family [transcripts], 1911 - 1914 January (Box 50)
  - VC 1914 — Everett, Marion (Willard) — to and from family and from Henry Rupe, 1911 January - 1913 June (Box 51)
  - VC Ex 1914 — Hawley, Dorothy (Winslow) Dutchy — to family, 1910 September - 1912 June (Box 52)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — from mother, 1911 October 12 (Box 140)
  - VC 1916 — Frantz, Edna (Bachman) — to Rosemarie Boyle, 1912-1916; (11 letters) (Box 68)
  - VC 1916 — Yocum, Helen (Woodbury) — from Elizabeth (French) Babbott (VC 1914), [No Year] August 12 (Box 140)
  - VC 1917 — Compton, Dorothy (Danforth) — to family, 1913 Fall - 1917 May (Box 65)
  - VC 1917 — Duncan, Doris (Bullard) — to Mrs. Charles Culver, 1914 December 2; (1 letter) (Box 67)
  - VC 1917 — Glover, Frances G. (Cheney) — to family, circa 1913-1917 (Box 199)
  - VC 1917 — Pollack, Mary (Culver) — to family, 1913-1917 (Box 57)
  - VC Ex 1917 — Vance, Gertrude (Pratt) — to and from family, 1913-1914; (16 letters) (Box 74)
    **Vance, Gertrude (Pratt): See also the Vassar College Gertrude Pratt Vance Papers.
  - VC 1918 — Quigley, Elizabeth — to family, undated; (1 letter) (Box 72)
  - VC Ex 1918 — Wright, Jean — to family, 1914-1915 (Box 185)
  - VC 1919 — Stickney, Helen A. — to Kenneth Brush (fiance), 1917 November - 1920 October 3 (Box 141)
  - VC 1920 — Schmitt, Dorothy (Prentiss) — to Mother, 1918; (1 letter) (Box 72)
  - VC Ex 1920 — McAndrew, Marjorie — from family, "Alice," Margaret Hunter, Hazel A. Ware (VC 1913), and Helen Strickney, 1916 August - 1917 April; (10 letters) (Box 71)
  - VC 1921 — Haines, Sarah H. — to Mrs. Albert Haines, 1918 October 17 (Box 75)
  - VC 1921 — Hunter, Amy L. — to Milton Perry Hunter, 1918 November 15 (Box 70)
  - VC 1921 — Schneider, Jean — from "Mama," (Box 212)
  - VC 1922 — Weston, Faith (Borton) — to family and from Mrs. Butterfield, 1918-1922 (Box 58)
  - VC 1923 — Aaron, Fannie Hamburger (Friedman) — to family, 1919-1923; (784 items) (Boxes 197-198)
    The papers of Fannie Aaron's brother and father (MS 621 Aaron Family Papers) are available at the American Jewish Archives in Cincinnati, Ohio.
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — to Dr and Mrs N. C. Barclay, 1919 October (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — to Barclay family, 1920 Spring - 1923 (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — to Dr. N. C. Barclay, 1920 June - 1923 (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — to Mrs. N. C. Barclay, undated (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from Mary Struckslager, undated (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from Mrs. N. C. Barclay, 1919 November 10 (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from VC Treasurer [receipt], 1919 December (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from Irene C. Riugwood, 1921 September 8 (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from [Phi Beta Kappa], undated (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — from Henry Noble MacCracken, 1923 March 7, June 21 (Box 145)
  - VC 1923 — Murphy, Lois (Barclay) — fragments, 1920-1923, undated (Box 145)
  - VC 1924 — Goldmark, Maxine — to family, 1920-1924, undated (Box 203)
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred F. — to Edith, 1920-1924; [5 folders] (Box 212)
  - VC 1925 — Brydon, Anne Page (Nancy) — to family and Robert Brydon and from Cleland and Jesse Mary Page, 1921-1925 (Box 59)
  - VC 1925 — Rose, Caroline (Averill) — to Caroline Rose and from Marjorie MacCracken, Emma Hibshman (VC 1924), Alice and Anna West (VC 1925), Roberta Whitehead (VC 1927), and others, 1922-1934, 1982 (Box 185)
  - VC 1927 — Bouck, Polly — to family, 1920-1931 (Box 188)
  - VC 1927 — Lurton, Sallie E. — to Edward Eager, 1924-1925 (Box 203)
  - VC 1928 — Chapman, Helen (Riesenfeld) — to parents, 1924-1927 (Box 196)
  - VC 1929 — Trask, Margaret (Pope) — to family, 1925 September - 1927 May (Box 60)
  - VC 1929 — Trask, Margaret (Pope) — to family, 1927 September - 1929 June (Box 61)
  - VC 1930 — Specht, Donaldine (Dudley) — to family, 1926-1930 (Boxes 162-168)
  - VC 1931 — Merrill, Margaret — to family and from mother, 1926-1930 (Box 187)
  - VC 1932 — Wright, Elizabeth (Fish) — to family, 1929-1932 (Box 210)
  - VC 1932 — Naudain, Florence A. — to Miss Wheeler, 1931-1932 (Box 71)
  - VC 1933 — Dick, Alice M. — to family, 1931 (Box 67)
  - VC 1935 — Delmas, Gladys (Krieble) — to family and from Jean Delmas, 1930 - circa 1960s (Boxes 171-176)
  - VC 1936 — White, Francis F. — to family and fiance, 1929-1941 (Box 189)
  - VC 1937 — Jack, Jane Anne (McKee) — to family and from Donald Berry, 1932 January - 1937 June (Box 62)
  - VC 1938 — Jackson, Agnes (Reynolds) — to Mary McCarthy, 1941 August 11 (Box 70)
  - VC 1941 — McCarthy, Mary (Fitt) — to family, 1941 June 9-30 (Box 71)
  - VC 1947 — Buyer, Suzanne Fructbaum — to family, 1944-1947 (Box 203)
  - VC 1948 — Allison, Ginia — to family, 1944-1945 (Box 207)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — to and from family, 1945 (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — from family, 1946; (2 folders) (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — to family, 1946 (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — from family, 1947 (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — to family, 1947 (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — to family, 1948 (Box 212)
  - VC 1949 — Birmingham, Barbara Price — Miscellaneous, 1945-1950, undated (Box 212)
  - VC 1952 — Jones, Jane (DeWalt) — to family, 1948-1952 (Box 182)
  - VC 1952 — Louden, Anne (Zimmerman) — to Robert K. Louden, 1948-1952 (Boxes 194-195)
  - VC 1957 — Alexander, Leah McClement — to mother, 1953-1957 (Box 211)
  - VC 1958 — Payne, Belinda J. Pope — to father, 1955 Jan 11 (Box 212)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Hannah" — to brother, 1866 October 18; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Anna" — to Mary C. Gauntlett, [1867?] September 22; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Emma" — to "Dell", 1868 October 18; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Nellie" — to mother, 1868 November 10; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Nellie" — to father, 1868 November 15; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Jeannette" — to Mary P. Ashbridge, 1869 September 22; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Mary" — to mother, 1870 March 5; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Mary" — to sister, "Mollie", 1872 November 24; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Katharine" — to mother, 1873 April 26; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Mary" — to "Mithery", 1876 June; (1 letter) (Box 64)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Ruth", 1894 February (Box 20)
  - VC Class Year Unknown — "Gert" — to family, 1918 February 13; (1 letter) (Box 64)
- SERIES VI. NOTEBOOKS, 1866-1974
  - VC 1867 — Bishop, Harriette A. (Warner) — Physical Geography (Box 94)
  - VC 1867 — Bishop, Harriette A. (Warner) — Geology and Zoology (Box 94)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Helen F. — Literature, 1867 (Box 111)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Helen F. — Mental Philosophy, undated (Box 111)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Helen F. — Literature, 1867 (Box 111)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Helen F. — Natural Philosophy (Box 111)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Helen F. — Philosophy, 1867 (Box 111)
  - VC 1868-1869 [Preparatory], 1869-1870 [Special] — Chase, Almira (Cowles) — 2 Chemistry (Box 95)
  - VC 1868-1869 [Preparatory], 1869-1870 [Special] — Chase, Almira (Cowles) — French (Box 95)
  - VC 1868-1869 [Preparatory], 1869-1870 [Special] — Chase, Almira (Cowles) — Natural Philosophy (Box 95)
  - VC 1873 — Brewer, Elizabeth H. — Problems in Trigonometry, 1871 (Box 207)
  - VC 1873 — Corliss, Lucy F. — Natural History [Orton], undated (Box 97)
  - VC 1873 — Richardson, Mary (Raymond) — English Literature, 1871 (Box 107)
  - VC Ex 1873 — Keene, Julia M. — French, 1869-1970 (Box 204)
  - VC Ex 1873 — Keene, Julia M. — English, undated (Box 207)
  - VC 1870-1874 [Special] — Tuttle, Mary R. — 2 Chemistry, 1872-1873 (Box 111)
  - VC 1875 — Barnes, Lucy (Sellers) — Science, undated (Box 95)
  - VC 1875 — Barnes, Lucy (Sellers) — Mental Philos., undated (Box 95)
  - VC Ex 1875 — Pidgeon, Mary (Kiersted)— Latin, undated (Box 99)
  - VC Ex 1875 — Pidgeon, Mary (Kiersted)— Architecture, undated (Box 103)
  - VC Ex 1875 — Wheeler, Helen (Lough)— Astronomy, undated (Box 112)
  - VC 1876 — Adams, Mary Louise "Minnie" (Kellogg) — Miscellaneous, including post-Vassar material, 1873-1879 (Box 119)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — Art and Chemistry, 1875 (Box 107)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — Astronomy, 1875-1876 (Box 107)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — Chemistry, undated (Box 108)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — Physiology (Box 108)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — 2 Misc. [Greek translations?], 1875, undated (Box 108)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — Mental Philosophy, German, Astronomy, 1875-1876 (Box 108)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — German, undated (Box 108)
  - VC 1876 — Scott, Mary Augusta — French and German, 1873 (Box 108)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Chemistry, 1875 (Box 109)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Physics, Geology, 1876 (Box 109)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — 3 Physics, 1876 (Box 109)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Natural Philosophy, 1876-1877 (Box 110)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Botany, undated (Box 110)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Cicero, undated (Box 110)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Poetry, undated (Box 110)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — Literature, undated (Box 110)
  - VC 1877 — Thompson, Mary (Thaw) — miscellaneous (Box 110)
  - VC 1878 — Wilkinson, Sarah G. — 2 Chemistry, undated (Box 114)
  - VC 1878 — Wilkinson, Sarah G. — Latin, undated (Box 113)
  - VC 1878 — Wilkinson, Sarah G. — Mental Philosophy, 1877 (Box 113)
  - VC 1878 — Wilkinson, Sarah G. — 2 Physics, 1877 (Box 113)
  - VC 1882 — Raymond, Cornelia M. — History (Box 105)
  - VC 1882 — Wheeler, Jessie F. — Botany, 1879 (Box 112)
  - VC 1883 — Fearrington, Mary (Pass) — Botany and Latin, 1879 (Box 97)
  - VC 1883 — Fearrington, Mary (Pass) — Chemistry, 1882 (Box 104)
  - VC 1890 — Griggs, Harriet F.— Botany, 1887 (Box 205)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— 3 History, 1887-1888 (Box 100)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Historical Geology, 1889 (Box 101)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Chemistry, 1888 (Box 101)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Latin and Greek, 1887 (Box 101)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Botany and Latin, [1888?] (Box 101)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Art History, 1889 (Box 102)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Hist of Literature, 1887 (Box 102)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Philosophy, 1889 (Box 102)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— German and Senior Literature, 1889-1890 (Box 102)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Literature, Latin, Physiology, 1887 (Box 103)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Rhetoric and Philology (Box 103)
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson)— Botany [pressed plants], 1881 (Box 118)
  - VC 1890 — Wheeler, Edith — unknown subject, 1886-1887 (Box 112)
  - VC Ex 1894 — Hawley, Ada (Brown) — Botany Samples, undated (Box 117)
  - VC 1896 — Black, Mignonette B. (Johnson) — Art History, 1894 (Box 103)
  - VC 1896 — Black, Mignonette B. (Johnson) — 2 Biology [lecture and lab], 1895 (Box 99)
  - VC 1896 — Smith, Gertrude Lydia (Chesley) — English Hist, 1897 Fall (Box 97)
  - VC 1896 — Smith, Gertrude Lydia (Chesley) — Prompters Bk: The Lady of the Lake, undated (Box 114)
  - VC Ex 1896 — DeWitt, Nettie (Brand)— [readings?], undated (Box 94)
  - VC Ex 1896 — DeWitt, Nettie (Brand) — English, 1894 (Box 94)
  - VC 1897 — Chesley, Mabel — Art History, 1894 (Box 97)
  - VC 1897 — Chesley, Mabel — Sociology, 1896 (Box 97)
  - VC 1897 — Chesley, Mabel — Economics, 1894 (Box 97)
  - VC Ex 1897 — Higbie, Florence W. — Greek, 1893-1894 (Box 100)
  - VC 1898 — Bacon, Mary (Taber) — Biology, 1897 (Box 94)
  - VC 1898 — Matthews, Helen (Whitman) — English, 1897 (Box 104)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Physics, 1896 (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Physics, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Physics Lab, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — History, 1896 (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — History, 1896 (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Psychology, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — English, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — English, undated (Box 190)
  - VC 1898 — Potter, Louise E. — Miscellaneous, 1895 (Box 190)
  - VC 1900 — Brand, Violet (Barnard) — Miscellaneous, undated (Box 94)
  - VC 1900 — Trowbridge, Isabel Bliss — "The Kleptic Ballads", undated (Box 153)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson)— 2 History, 1900-1902 (Box 105)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — English, 1902 (Box 106)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — Literature, 1901 (Box 106)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — Shakespeare, 1901 (Box 106)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — Ethics, 1902 (Box 106)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — Geology, 1901 (Box 107)
  - VC 1903 — Reed, Elizabeth (Thompson) — Physiology, 1902 (Box 107)
  - VC 1905 — Ross, Caroline (Barnes) — [Physiology?] (Box 93)
  - VC 1905 — Ross, Caroline (Barnes) — Physiology Lab (Box 93)
  - VC 1907 — Wilson, Mary Constance — Social Psychology (Box 213)
  - VC 1908 — Phipard, L. Elisabeth — Chemistry, circa 1904-1908 (Box 119)
  - VC 1908 — Phipard, L. Elisabeth — Philosophy, circa 1904-1908 (Box 119)
  - VC 1908 — Phipard, L. Elisabeth — Architecture, circa 1904-1908 (Box 119)
  - VC 1908 — Phipard, L. Elisabeth — 3 History, circa 1904-1908 (Box 119)
  - VC 1910 — Somerville, Carol — Chemistry, undated (Box 109)
  - VC 1911 — Carter, Mary — "Ethics" (Box 116)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — Art, 1908-1910 (Box 96)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — English, 1908-1909 (Box 96)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — English, 1909-1910 (Box 96)
  - VC 1911 — Chase, G. Louise (Fletcher) — History [Salmon Historical Materials], 1911 February - May (Box 115)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Psychology, 1908-1909 (Box 157)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Psychology, 1909-1910 (Box 157)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — [Biology], 1910 (Box 157)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — VC Song Book (Box 157)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Psychology, undated (Box 158)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Genetic Psychology, undated (Box 158)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford) — Psychology, undated (Box 158)